A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
I brought it. You'll remove one of the snakes from inside me now, like you said you would, right?
Of course. You've done well, Erika. Good work.
Finally. Free, how was your magic eye?
Ah, in perfect shape now. I should be able to control an independent cube easily.
With that eye, the Grand Witch was an expert in spatial magic.
Now that the magic eye belongs to you, you'll be needed tonight.
Erika and I will be lending you support with computation spells. We're counting on you.
Yeah, just leave it to me.
Now, the time has come.
I've been waiting for this night.
六人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに 惹きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
It'll start without us if you don't hurry.
You're the one who took forever with all the primping you had to do
Hey, Sol, I'm gonna eat a bunch of food until I puke
Oh, gentlemanly
Over here, guys
Hey, take a look at these guys. They're dressed up all fancy pants
What's wrong, kid? You don't seem very excited
Oh, I'm sorry
I'm so hungry
How gentlemanly
Anyway, everybody, thank you so much for coming
Tonight, we celebrate the founding of the DWMA
The eve party nightmare, and so the curtain rises?
Please, come inside. My father will be giving his greetings shortly
Oh, hungry
Can what father told me actually be true?
Something like that exists here?
Hello
Hey, hiya
Thanks for coming. But great to see you
It's Lord Death
Wow, Lord Death
Okay, well, that's about all I have to say
Have a great time tonight
That was kinda short
Father isn't taking this seriously
All, if I may speak as well
Thank you for taking the time to come here
Tonight at this gala, we celebrate something dear to all of our hearts
The founding of our academy
If you will kindly indulge me
I, Death the Kid, would like to say a few words
Man, he's a real pro
We all know the mission of this school
To maintain peace in this world
It's me, in all my glory
The one and only amazing black star, yeah
Of course, this is all thanks to
Hear me people, it's me with a capital M
I'm the only one big enough to capitalize me
Anyway, as I was saying
Disgusted Dash
What do you think you're doing?
You can't interrupt my big speech
You're the one who interrupt it, you hopeless idiot
I wanted my speech to be precise and exact
It's ruined
I want to die
That jerk
Whose party does he think this is, anyway?
You do realize it's not yours, don't you?
Well, is this a party or isn't it?
There's a band and lots of food
So eat, sing, dance, do the hokey pokey
Whatever you're in the mood for
Yeah
There he goes
Kick your legs up to a 90 degree angle
They should match perfectly
Okay
How embarrassing
This kind of fancy party really isn't my scene
Sol
Huh?
Hey Mako, what's up?
The food's great tonight, don't you want to eat something?
Uh...
I don't feel like standing in line for some fancy food
Besides, eating while you're standing up is awkward
You're missing out, Sol
The stuff is delicious
Fine, then give me some of yours
Nope
Food hog
How's Sol?
Is he still having that strange dream with the demon in it?
He seemed to be quite troubled by it
Uh, Sol?
It seems like something's been eating at you lately
Huh?
What makes you say that?
I'm sorry
I thought he would've told you about it
He told me
You can talk to me about these things, you know
Sure, but nothing's wrong
Uh...
What is it?
I probably shouldn't pry too much into it
So...
That's how it is
You think I'm an unreliable partner, don't you?
You said it, not me
Whatever!
Like, you have any room to talk
You're not so great
Yeah!
Let's dance
Huh?
Forget about it
I don't wanna
Oh, come on
You know you're a good dancer, Sol
I'll let you lead
Besides, dancing is good for matching Sol wavelengths
So quit arguing
Hold it right there!
Huh?
Come dance with your papa!
No way
Talk about perfect timing
All children need to bond with their parents, Maka
You should go dance with him
I don't feel like bonding
Sol is exactly right
Let's dance, Maka
I'm ready to win
I'm coming, Sol
Guard my food, will you?
She wants me to guard her food
Yet she refused to let me have any
Huh?
She can't stand raw fish
What is she doing getting salmon from the buffet?
Fickle woman
Oh...
It's for me
That was dumb
It's not like I need any help from her
Oh, well
It does look good
Medusa, we've entered Death City
What do you want us to do now?
Wait at the designated spot for the signal from us
One more thing
Have we obtained the assistance we need?
It's all set
Krona
Or should I say Ragnarok
Will be leading them here soon
All right
Good work, Erika
Well, hello there, Dr. Medusa
You're having fun, I hope
Oh, hello, Professor Stein
My, you're always sneaking up on me
This guy again
You should go ahead and drink that before I do
Cheers
Are you all right, Professor Stein?
Oh, sorry, I'm a bit drunk
I must have had too much champagne
Is he faking it? I can't read it
What do you say? Let's go dancing
Come on, don't be a party
We're all dressed up in everything
No, no, no, no
Someone help
Know what I'm thinking about, Maka?
The last time we danced
It was the day of your kindergarten graduation
You danced on my feet
And then afterwards, I danced with your mama
What a great day
It wasn't mama you were dancing with
It was actually Sarah's mother
Oh, crap, was it really?
Oh, boy, did I screw that one up
Leave it to Maka to remember that far back
Anyway, I'm dancing with you now
And that's what counts, isn't it?
Tonight will be a great memory
I promise you, Maka
I'm going to be a better papa
No way
What am I doing?
I have to get off this dance floor
I can't let Erika and the others see me like this
Dr. Medusa?
Ugh
Hmm
Professor Sid has been gone for quite a while now
Do you know anything about that?
Oh?
I'm afraid I don't know anything that could help you
I do hope he's alright, though
You're sure you don't know?
Hmm
He went to investigate a laboratory somewhere
Now let me think here
Who did that laboratory belong to again?
Oh, that's right, it was your laboratory
I have no idea what you're talking about, Professor
I'm curious to know why a witch like you would risk coming to the DWMA
You really are quite drunk, aren't you?
Perhaps I should bring you a glass of water
I can do without the water, thank you
I wasn't really drunk
I take it the Keishan is what you're interested in
I find it hard to imagine you snuck into the academy just to observe what goes on with all of our weapons and Meisters
More likely, you know about it, don't you, Witch Medusa?
About the Keishan sleeping beneath the DWMA
Hmm
You hopeless fool
If it weren't for Lord Death being here, you'd be dead now
Shall we cut to the chase?
No need to hold back
I found you out, you can drop the charade
Alright then
You're correct, my goal is to revive the Keishan
And for that you needed black blood
But why? What does it do?
The Keishan's power surpasses human understanding
It is evolution itself
Lord Death and his little academy have monitored and protected the world by acting as a check against power
The DWMA seeks only to maintain the status quo
That's its mission
But still, time continues to march forward
It's only natural for the rest of the world to progress with it, don't you agree?
That's how nature works
And yet, Professor Stein
This academy has made a point to keep that from happening
Do you really want to live in a world of stasis where nothing changes?
You're a scientist like me
Surely you must understand
So...
Why don't you join me?
Sky!
Hurry!
Everyone get out of here immediately
Professor Cid?
Are you okay?
Yeah
But I'm not sure how
We ran into an ambush
we ran into an ambush i dove underground right before the blast but i barely got away
what we need to do now is get everyone out of here it's a trap this is the day they've been
waiting for when lord death leaves his mirror and all of the students and teachers are in one place
medusa free the barrier now trap them all inside right i'm on it now soul protect release
what is that wolf wolves wolf wolves this will prevent any interference anyone who gets trapped
inside this magic box will be unable to escape erica hurry we need to get the box's position set
ribbit ribbit computation spell magic calculation
what what is this it's starting now nygas you ready we need soul resonance yeah
we have to get these guys out appearance position confirmed spatial magic independent cube now
this is gonna be close
what's happening out there what's going on i'm sensing something i can feel a spatial warping
that's it they're locking us in here we go
coffins what are these for
uh
no sin we're counting on you to protect the dwma
we've got one hour medusa it won't hold longer than that in that case let's get gone before death
shows up we don't have a single second to waste where's crona
i brought them just like you say the mizune family
the only reason they came to help was because i lied and said that the academy killed the oldest
that was mizune sister i had to do it but i'm so sorry mizune's
i'll leave the rest in your mousy little hands bring death city crashing down around their heads
erica you've got the attache case right here we're headed underground
i will revive the kishin
the meisters landed on their feet and the weapons didn't i guess we really are different
i'm sensing some witch souls up there one two eight of them and the demon sword also
what was that what are they doing up there listen up kids we've got an emergency on our hands
below the dwma sleeps a kishin the source of all madness in the world you should know our school nurse
medusa is a witch she snuck into the academy to revive the kishin we must stop this at all costs
dr medusa is actually a witch professor that's crazy and this kishin too how something like that
beneath the school it's true my father explained everything to me in order to keep the kishin
sleeping safe and sound my father cannot ever leave the academy huh so there's a reason lord death
never goes anywhere i always thought he just wasn't much of a people person let's get moving we can't
let sid's quick thinking go to waste all of you follow me i'll take us to the entrance that leads underground
it didn't budge oh my we're in a real pickle here yep quite a predicament lord death
you need to get out of here sir can you escape through this a mirror unfortunately that's a no
can do you see there wouldn't be anywhere to go this space is cut off from all other worlds at best
a high octane spell like this will only hold up for an hour or so there isn't a whole lot we can do until
then oh i understand sorry about that kid
damn we've been acting so complacent we're just too used to peace hey now there's nothing wrong
with being used to peace i think we should get more used to it because that would mean the world
is a peaceful place so we're gonna sit here preserving the peace because that's what this academy
was built for as for the rest of it it's all up to them this is the entrance we need
our enemy is powerful if you aren't prepared for what lies ahead then you may die
if you want to turn around better do it now
are you ready to fight against fear itself will you cross beyond that door
let your souls make the decision for you
we're coming good
you
Thank you.
Let's fight. Let's do this. I'm ready. Let's get going.
Whoa, Sol. You're too worked up. Calm down a little, okay?
What are you talking about? Why shouldn't I be pumped right now?
In situations like this, you need to keep your cool.
Let's try a little exercise. Repeat after me.
I will be cool.
Sounds kind of dumb to me, but fine. I will be cool. I will be cool.
Okay, can we fight now?
Oh, never mind.
On the next episode of Sol Eater, the underground battle commences.
Break through Medusa's vector arrow?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.